factly.com 2010-12-30

# Factly | Information You Need

**

Factly Privacy Policy

**   
General. Factly places great importance in protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy is designed to explain the manner in which Factly collects, uses, and discloses the personal information provided by you as a result of the use of Factly's Web Site and the content, information and services provided through the Web Site by Factly. 

**

Users' Consent.

** **BY ACCESSING THIS WEB SITE AND/OR ANY OTHER SITE PROVIDED BY FACTLY (COLLECTIVELY, THE "SITE"), YOU ARE SIGNIFYING, EXPRESSING AND PROVIDING YOUR CONSENT TO THE INFORMATION COLLECTION, INFORMATION USAGE, AND OTHER PROCEDURES DESCRIBED IN THE PRIVACY POLICY BELOW.**

Factly reserves the right to change this policy at any time, without notice, by posting a new privacy policy at this location. The collection, use and disclosure of your personal information by Factly will be governed by the version of this Policy in effect at that time. Please check this page periodically for any changes. Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy. Types and uses of personal information. In order to contribute, post comments and mark favorite articles on our Sites, you must first create an account with a username and password; we use these to provide you with access to your profile and comments. Our registration system also requires that you provide a valid email address; we use that to confirm your account. Accounts in our system are perpetual. If you change the information in your account, our stored data backups may include your original information for up to six months. Separately, when you email us, we retain your address and correspondence. We use these to raise and respond to issues and inquiries of all types. 

Information Sharing and Disclosure. Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable):We share aggregated demographic information about our reader base with our third-party advertising partners, including browser information and traffic statistics. We do not link this data to individual readers' accounts or personally identifiable information. Personally identifiable information:We do not share personally identifiable information with third parties, with one limited exception: we may disclose personally identifiable information about you if we have a good faith belief that doing so is required by law, such as pursuant to a subpoena or other judicial or administrative order. Internet Protocol Addresses. We collect the IP addresses of all visitors to our Site. We use your IP address in order to administer the Site, help diagnose problems with our server, to gather broad demographic information, and for the "User Tracking" described above. Cookies. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. The information we store in cookies is, in some cases, linked to readers' accounts. We use both short-term cookies and persistent cookies. A short-term cookie expires within a limited period of time. We use session cookies so that readers with accounts can navigate and contribute to our site without logging in multiple times over a short period of time. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. We use persistent cookies to recognize account holders and present the site accordingly. You can remove cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as comments, will require logging in for each action you want to take. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by the Site only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

Third-party Advertisers. The ads appearing on this Site are delivered to readers by various ad networks which may place or recognize unique cookies on your browser and use information about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services. The information collected does not include personally identifiable information like your name, address, email address or telephone number. It does include IP addresses, though these are not tied to individual readers' accounts. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Factly.com. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**Links to Other Sites.**

This Site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Factly.com. Please be aware that we, the Site is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Site. 

**Changes in This Privacy Statement.**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

**Other.**

The applicable law and exclusive jurisdiction for settling any disputes in connection with the use of the Site shall be the laws and jurisdiction of the state of California according to the provisions of the then policy in effect. In order to assist in protecting the confidentiality of your personal information, Factly applies security safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the information. However, in light of the nature of Internet technologies, security and privacy risks cannot be eliminated and, therefore, Factly cannot guarantee that your personal information will not be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Policy. 

**Last Updated: February 6, 2009**
